Better head to work.
It's about 60,000 a month \Nfor cutting down trees, right?
Then there's the kidney I sold. \NThat was 1.2 million.
My right eye was 300,000.
Sold one of my nuts...
How much was that, again? \NI think... not even 100,000.
And I still owe...
About 38,040,000 yen.
I heard you, Pochita.
Let's kill this thing already.
A dead devil's usually good \Nfor about 300,000...
Devil hunting pays the best, easy.
Gotta be the Tomato Devil.
He'll revive from the seeds, \Nso you'll wanna burn those.
Nice work, Denji.
This carcass will bring in a fair \Nprice on the black market.
I'll pay you 400,000.
Hey, thanks!
After what you owe and \Nthe interest, that leaves 170,000.
So after the finder's fee, admin fee,
management costs, and so on...
Leaves me with 70,000.
After the water bill, \Nand some other stuff I owe...
Funny how that works.
I've got 1,800 yen left.
No food at home, and this is gonna \Nhave to last us a month, so...
Pochita, looks like dinner's \Ngonna be a slice of bread.
Why hire a brat like that to hunt devils?
He's paying off what he owes us.
Well, technically, it was \Nhis deadbeat old man's debt.
And a kid with a pet devil \Ncan get the job done?
The thing about real devil hunters is...
They don't pass devil \Ncarcasses onto the yakuza.
Besides, the best thing about Denji \Nis he does what he's told.
Hey, dog!
I'll give you 100 yen to eat this cigarette.
For real?
Don't mind if I do.
We'll be in touch \Nwhen there's another devil.
Try and run, and you're pig slop.
That'll keep us for another three days.
The other day I heard...
That normally, people put jam \Non their bread, before eating it.
Normal's just a dream for us, though.
Doubt I'll pay off this debt before I die.
Probably gonna die without \Never having a girlfriend, too.
Not like I could invite a girl to this dump.
No money to go on dates, either.
If I could have one dream come true...
I wanna score with a girl before I die.
Bastard hung himself without \Npaying this month's installment first.
Boy, you've got until tomorrow \Nto put 700,000 together.
You can beg for it, whore yourself out...\N I don't care. Get it done.
Otherwise, we chop you up and sell the bits.
A ch-chainsaw...?
A devil.
If you're gonna kill me, just do it. \NI'm dead either way.
It's hurt?
You're gonna die, too?
Bite me!
I heard that drinking blood heals a devil.
If you don't wanna die, bite me!
My blood's not free, though. This is a deal!
I'll help you...
So, you help me.
Because I don't wanna die, after all.
Why don't you hire me as a devil hunter?
Too hungry to sleep.
When I can't sleep, \NI start thinking about money,
and then it's even harder to sleep.
I know what dream I wanna have when I sleep.
Gonna put jam on my bread, \Nand share it with you.
Then I'm gonna flirt with a girl...
I'll play video games with her, and then \Nwe'll fall asleep hugging each other.
Sounds sweet, right?
Y'know, I heard my mom died from some \Nheart disease that made her cough up blood.
Got a devil for you, Denji. Time for work.
Wish they'd at least let me dream...
There's a devil in here, huh?
I don't see anything.
You think it's hiding?
Or maybe it left already?
Denji, my boy... we're pretty \Ngrateful to you, y'know?
Yeah?
You're as loyal as a dog,
and you work for cheap like one, too.
Only problem with dogs \Nis I can't stand the stench.
Even yakuza think about getting bigger \Nand making more money, kid.
So we did like you, \Nand made a deal with a devil.
We wanted demonic power...
And I want devil hunters...
Dead!
Y'know, little devil hunter, \Nthese guys are dumb as hell.
Total suckers!
I offer them a bit of demonic power, \Nand they offer to become my slaves...
Even though the power \Nturns them into zombies.
See, because I'm the Zombie Devil.
And I hate devil hunters, because you\N go around killing us devils.
So I'm gonna kill you.
Boys, tear him apart \Nand toss him in the trash.
Shit!
How do I get out of here?
Get off!
It's not like I'm asking to be rich.
All I want is a normal life!
And I can't even have that?!
Pochita...
Pochita!
Pochita, time for work.
Pochita, there's a good chance \NI'm gonna die fighting a devil.
My only regret would be \Nleaving you on your own.
You could end up starving to death...
Or some other devil hunter might kill you.
I've heard some devils \Ncan take over dead bodies.
If that's something you can do... \Nthen I want you to have my body.
The yakuza won't be on your case \Nif you wait until I've been buried, right?
And then you could move \Nout of here... and then...
Yeah.
I want you to live a normal life, \Nand die a normal death.
You've gotta make my dream come true.
Pochita?
Did you take my body, like I said?
I always loved hearing you talk \Nabout your dreams, Denji.
Here's the deal. I'll give you my heart...
And in exchange, I want you \Nto show me your dream.
Pochita?!
I'm not hurt?
Pochita...?
What is this?
You're alive after being sliced up?
Why? Gross!
I seriously hate devil hunters.
Guys, go ahead and eat him.
These guys had plenty already, \Nso why'd they want even more?
Am I the same?
I wasn't satisfied with \Nthe happiness I had with Pochita.
I kept dreaming about a better life.
I guess we all dream \Nabout stuff like that, huh?
I can't blame you, then.
And I won't, but...
If you get in our way?
You'll die!
He's bound to stay dead after being eaten.
What are you?!
Did that devil runt take your body?!
That means you're one of us!
Ow...
It hurts!
Stay away!
Move!
Stay back! Back! Get away!
Stay away! Don't do it!
Don't come near me!
Die!
I guess you guys went full devil, huh?
Well, you hired me to be a devil hunter.
So, I better kill all the devils, right?!
Oh, yeah!
Once you're all dead...
I won't owe a damn thing!
Someone got here before us.
There's still one alive.
You've got a strange smell.
Not like a human or a devil.
I take it you did this?
H-Hug me...
He's human.
Any chance he's possessed?
No.
I can tell who's possessed \Nwith a look at their face.
I came here to kill the Zombie Devil.
I'm a devil hunter with Public Safety.
You have two options:
I can kill you like a devil,
or I can keep you as a human.
If I keep you, I'll make sure you're fed.
When you say that...
Like, what's for breakfast?
Bread with butter and jam, salad, coffee...
And then maybe something \Nfor dessert, I think?
That sounds awesome.
That was my stomach.
What's your name?
It's Denji!
I need to tell you something right now.
From now on, you're in my care, Denji.
I expect "yes" or "woof" for answers. \NI don't need a dog that says "no."
When you say that...
Someone in forensics once told me...
That when we get dogs that \Naren't helpful, we put them down.
I thought she was nice.
I kind of liked her.
I had no idea she was scary like this.
Treating me like a damn dog...
I just remembered how Pochita's dead.
General
We haven't had breakfast yet, either. \NLet's grab something at the rest area.
Sorry, but I don't have any cash.
Just pick what you want. I'll pay.
And you're conspicuous \Nwithout a shirt on, so wear this.
Here.
All my life people have avoided me, \Nsaying I'm filthy and smell bad.
No one's ever been nice to me before.
Much less a girl who looks this good!
I love her!
I'll take some udon...
Udon and... a sausage!
Is that cool?
Sure is. I'll take a curry udon, please.
Coming up.
Oh, that sounds good, too...
Whoa, there.
Denji? You okay?
You smell good.
How much will it be?
Gimme one sec...
Denji?
It'll be 1,100 yen, all together.
The chainsaws cut me up, too,
Here's 2,000.
so I think I'm a little \Nlow on blood right now.
How did you end up like this?
I had a pet devil, and he replaced my heart.
Kinda hard to believe, huh?
I don't really wanna believe it, either.
Pochita dying for my sake...
There's not a lot of precedent \Nfor your condition,
even from a historical perspective.
It doesn't even have a name.
I believe you.
I've got a particularly good sense of smell.
So I can tell.
Your best friend is alive inside of you.
Not in the sentimental sense, either.
Your body has the scents \Nof both a human and a devil.
Is that right?
That's awesome!
Really... awesome...
Udon?!
The udon?
Is it cool if I eat my udon?
Are you all right? \NCan you eat on your own?
I can...
I can not.
Here. Say, "Ahh."
Ahh...
Is it good?
Woof!
You are really sweet to be \Nenjoying soggy udon this much.
A lot like a dog, actually.
Um... what's your name?
Makima.
Miss Makima... is there a type\N of guy you l-like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
Denji?
Dude, that's me.
Is there a type of guy you like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
I like you, too, Miss Makima.
Denji? This way, come on.
This is the Tokyo headquarters \Nfor our Devil Hunters.
There are over a thousand Devil Hunters \Nin Tokyo, including civilians,
but Public Safety has the best benefits \Nand a lot of paid vacation time.
If Miss Makima likes me...
Then maybe, if we work together, \Nwe'll eventually get together?
And if we get together... \Nwe can get together, right?
I wanna! I wanna get together \Nwith her real bad!
Denji...
Yeah?
We're supposed to \Nwear uniforms, so put this on.
Once you've changed, \NI'll introduce you to a coworker.
This is Aki Hayakawa. He started \Nthree years before you, Denji.
You're going to be shadowing him today.
I'm not working with you, Miss Makima?
That should be obvious.
You're not even in her league.
Time for patrol.
No! Miss Makima!
Damn it, get up.
No way! I wanna work with Miss Makima!
If you do a good job, \Nwe can work together someday.
So, do that, okay?
Hey, big man.
Does Miss Makima have a boyfriend?
Hey, come on.
Hey!
Come with me.
You need to quit this job.
Show up tomorrow, \Nand I'll kick your ass again.
Why, though?
Look, I'm trying to be nice, here.
People who start this job without \Nthinking it through end up dead.
I've had colleagues who got \Ninto devil hunting for the payday,
and it got them all killed by devils.
The survivors are the ones \Nwith real motivation.
You're just after Makima, right? \NThat's why you took the job?
Ding-ding!
Then I'm glad I hit you.
I'll let her know that you ran off, \Nscared away by the devils.
You really are a nice guy, huh?
Because... when I fight a dude...
It's nuts... or nothing!
I had udon for the first time today, man.
A sausage, too.
Got treated like a decent \Nhuman being for the first time,
and even had someone pay for my meal.
It's like a dream come true for me.
I didn't really think it through \Nwhen I started devil hunting,
but if I get to keep up this kind of life?
I don't care if it kills me.
Actually, y'know, I take it back.
It's not just my life, anymore.
Makima...
is not the kind of woman \Na punk like you should be chasing!
What the hell are you saying?
Sounds to me like you just like her, too!
You... really did...
Only aim... for my balls...
Shit.
The big guy's testicles were attacked \Nby the Nut Devil, ma'am!
That's a lie. He's lying.
So, do you think you two can work together?
No way!
He's a piece of trash!
I'm glad you two are hitting it off.
Denji, you're going to \Nbe joining Hayakawa's unit.
Unit?
This punk?!
I've already got enough \Ntroublemakers, don't I?
Adding another... I don't know...
I told you when I put it together, right?
Your team's an experimental one, \Noperating differently from the usual method.
What exactly is he, ma'am?
Denji's human, but can \Ntransform into a devil.
Damn right! Pretty sweet, huh?
And that's the truth?
I always figured those stories \Nwere baseless rumors.
He's special.
Which is why he's going to be \Nreceiving special treatment.
If he tries to resign, \Nor becomes insubordinate...
Denji will be disposed of as a devil.
Uh, what's that mean?
It means we're working \Ntogether until you die.
You're going to be living with me \Nso I can keep an eye on you.
Just remember, they said I can \Nkill you if you try to run off.
Hey, is Miss Makima a bad person?
If you think that's the case, \Nthen give up on her.
If you're really a devil, you should \Njust be grateful she doesn't kill you.
We're Devil Hunters, got that?
So, she's a good person, then?
Of course she is.
She saved my life.
Miss Makima...
I hope I get to hug her again.
Strawberry jam, plum jam, orange jam...
Then some butter and honey, plus...
Let's throw some cinnamon on, too.
I got the best toast ever right here!
So good!
It's freaking fantastic!
How long are you gonna be in there?!
Don't fall asleep on the toilet!
A Fiend has been reported \Nin an east Nerima residence.
Civilian evacuation and cordon \Nare both complete.
The Fiend in question has \Nholed up in a second story room.
We'll leave it to you \NDevil Hunters from here.
Is this a new rookie, Hayakawa?
Hey, what's a Fiend?
Did you never go to school or something?
Nah, man, no.
When a devil takes control \Nof a human corpse, you get a Fiend.
Wait, doesn't that make me a Fiend?
No. Fiends always have characteristic heads.
Should be obvious enough once we see him.
The devil controls a Fiend's personality.\N You kill this one.
Turn into a devil, \Nand show me what you can do.
That'll help me figure out \Nif you're of any use.
Don't look at me...
You're dead! Dead, dead, dead!
Damn Devil Hunters!
Hey. Why didn't you use your devil powers?
Thing is...
When I kill devils with my powers, \Nthey get real messed up.
So, like... I coulda ended up \Nlike this Fiend, right?
So I kinda... wanted to \Nmake it painless for him.
All right. Listen to me.
Fiends are just like any other devil.
If you're hunting them, \Nthen drop the sympathy.
My entire family was killed \Nby a devil right in front of me.
I've had drinks with the cops down below.
They're risking their lives \Nto protect their wives and kids.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
I'd rather make any devil I kill \Nsuffer as much as possible.
What are you trying to do? \NMake friends with them?
If there's a devil I could be \Nfriends with, then yeah, I would.
'Cuz I don't have any friends.
I'll remember that.
Guess I pissed him off...
I was just trying to keep \Nblood off these dirty magazines.
When the chainsaws are out, blood gets \Neverywhere and makes a real mess.
I made it easy for you, \Nso I get to keep these!
Okay, the porn is secured.
I want you to show me your dream.
I'm pretty serious about this, Pochita.
I'm already living the dream, \Njust like our bargain said.
I'll remember that.
My dream might've come true already, \Nbut he must be chasing his.
I get to bathe every day, eat good food...
Get to hang around a hot chick...
My life's a 10 outta 10, but it feels \Nlike something's missing.
Am I missing something? Something that'd\N give me a real perfect score?
He's gotta be after some revenge shit.
They're trying to protect their families.
I wonder if Miss Makima \Nis after anything like that?
Miss Makima...
I wanna touch her boobs.
Touching boobs is a dream I gave\N up on a long time ago,
but I've got a real job now. \NMaybe I could pull it off?
I probably couldn't score \Nwith a girl just yet.
But boobs?
If I had the right plan, and the\N willpower, then maybe...
Everyone is serious about this except you.
So that's what he meant!
I've found it! Something to be serious about!
My goal! It's...
Boobs!
Boobs?
Hey! Pay attention, dumbass!
Listen to what?
I'm assigning you a partner \Nstarting today, Denji.
Partner?
As a precaution, Public Safety executes patrols
and smaller missions with two-person teams.
This is great timing. She's here.
Be careful. She's a Fiend.
Prostrate yourselves, humans!
For I am Power!
Are you to be my so-called partner?!
Power?! Your name's Power?!
And you're a Fiend?!
Are Fiends allowed to be Devil Hunters?!
Well, whatever! Nice to meet you!
Fiends, like devils, \Nare targets for extermination.
But Power's highly rational,
so she's been on Hayakawa's team.
I mentioned this before,
but Public Safety Devil Extermination \NSpecial Division 4 is an experimental unit.
The higher-ups will be looking \Nto dissolve your team as soon as possible
if you can't get results.
I don't need to explain what would happen \Nto you two if that happens, do I?
Power's horns stand out a bit too much,
so you'll want to patrol areas \Nwithout a lot of pedestrians.
Human! Provide me with something \Nto kill immediately!
I am starved for blood!
I can put up with crazy, \Nas long as she's hot enough.
The question is, how do I get \Nmy hands on those boobs?
If you run into any civilian Devil Hunters,
or the police try to question you \Nabout what you're doing...
We've got a pair of suspicious individuals...
Excuse me, I need to ask you—
We're with Public Safety Devil \NExtermination Special Division 4.
...say that, show them your ID,
and they'll make a sour face \Nand leave you alone.
Where the hell are all the devils?!
This is likely my fault!
Before becoming a Fiend, \NI was a devil that was feared by all!
Demonic peons will likely flee \Nthe moment they catch my scent!
Wait, how are we gonna \Nget anything done, then?!
If you have any questions, \Njust ask Hayakawa.
He's the one who put you two together.
That asshole! He set me up!
He stuck me with Power \Nso I can't do anything cool!
He's trying to get me fired!
The scent of blood!
Whoa! Hey, crazy, where you going?!
The game is afoot!
The battle is joined!
Damn, she's fast!
The scene's evacuated and blocked off.
It's the Sea Cucumber Devil. \NYes, the Sea Cucumber Devil.
Requesting backup \Nin front of Nerima Station.
I said, it's the Sea Cucumber—
Do you know what a sea cucumber is?
Look, I'm trying to say—
What the...?
Did you see?! The kill is mine!