Better head to work.
It's about 60,000 a month \Nfor cutting down trees, right?
Then there's the kidney I sold. \NThat was 1.2 million.
My right eye was 300,000.
Sold one of my nuts...
How much was that, again? \NI think... not even 100,000.
And I still owe...
About 38,040,000 yen.
I heard you, Pochita.
Let's kill this thing already.
A dead devil's usually good \Nfor about 300,000...
Devil hunting pays the best, easy.
Gotta be the Tomato Devil.
He'll revive from the seeds, \Nso you'll wanna burn those.
Nice work, Denji.
This carcass will bring in a fair \Nprice on the black market.
I'll pay you 400,000.
Hey, thanks!
After what you owe and \Nthe interest, that leaves 170,000.
So after the finder's fee, admin fee,
management costs, and so on...
Leaves me with 70,000.
After the water bill, \Nand some other stuff I owe...
Funny how that works.
I've got 1,800 yen left.
No food at home, and this is gonna \Nhave to last us a month, so...
Pochita, looks like dinner's \Ngonna be a slice of bread.
Why hire a brat like that to hunt devils?
He's paying off what he owes us.
Well, technically, it was \Nhis deadbeat old man's debt.
And a kid with a pet devil \Ncan get the job done?
The thing about real devil hunters is...
They don't pass devil \Ncarcasses onto the yakuza.
Besides, the best thing about Denji \Nis he does what he's told.
Hey, dog!
I'll give you 100 yen to eat this cigarette.
For real?
Don't mind if I do.
We'll be in touch \Nwhen there's another devil.
Try and run, and you're pig slop.
That'll keep us for another three days.
The other day I heard...
That normally, people put jam \Non their bread, before eating it.
Normal's just a dream for us, though.
Doubt I'll pay off this debt before I die.
Probably gonna die without \Never having a girlfriend, too.
Not like I could invite a girl to this dump.
No money to go on dates, either.
If I could have one dream come true...
I wanna score with a girl before I die.
Bastard hung himself without \Npaying this month's installment first.
Boy, you've got until tomorrow \Nto put 700,000 together.
You can beg for it, whore yourself out...\N I don't care. Get it done.
Otherwise, we chop you up and sell the bits.
A ch-chainsaw...?
A devil.
If you're gonna kill me, just do it. \NI'm dead either way.
It's hurt?
You're gonna die, too?
Bite me!
I heard that drinking blood heals a devil.
If you don't wanna die, bite me!
My blood's not free, though. This is a deal!
I'll help you...
So, you help me.
Because I don't wanna die, after all.
Why don't you hire me as a devil hunter?
Too hungry to sleep.
When I can't sleep, \NI start thinking about money,
and then it's even harder to sleep.
I know what dream I wanna have when I sleep.
Gonna put jam on my bread, \Nand share it with you.
Then I'm gonna flirt with a girl...
I'll play video games with her, and then \Nwe'll fall asleep hugging each other.
Sounds sweet, right?
Y'know, I heard my mom died from some \Nheart disease that made her cough up blood.
Got a devil for you, Denji. Time for work.
Wish they'd at least let me dream...
There's a devil in here, huh?
I don't see anything.
You think it's hiding?
Or maybe it left already?
Denji, my boy... we're pretty \Ngrateful to you, y'know?
Yeah?
You're as loyal as a dog,
and you work for cheap like one, too.
Only problem with dogs \Nis I can't stand the stench.
Even yakuza think about getting bigger \Nand making more money, kid.
So we did like you, \Nand made a deal with a devil.
We wanted demonic power...
And I want devil hunters...
Dead!
Y'know, little devil hunter, \Nthese guys are dumb as hell.
Total suckers!
I offer them a bit of demonic power, \Nand they offer to become my slaves...
Even though the power \Nturns them into zombies.
See, because I'm the Zombie Devil.
And I hate devil hunters, because you\N go around killing us devils.
So I'm gonna kill you.
Boys, tear him apart \Nand toss him in the trash.
Shit!
How do I get out of here?
Get off!
It's not like I'm asking to be rich.
All I want is a normal life!
And I can't even have that?!
Pochita...
Pochita!
Pochita, time for work.
Pochita, there's a good chance \NI'm gonna die fighting a devil.
My only regret would be \Nleaving you on your own.
You could end up starving to death...
Or some other devil hunter might kill you.
I've heard some devils \Ncan take over dead bodies.
If that's something you can do... \Nthen I want you to have my body.
The yakuza won't be on your case \Nif you wait until I've been buried, right?
And then you could move \Nout of here... and then...
Yeah.
I want you to live a normal life, \Nand die a normal death.
You've gotta make my dream come true.
Pochita?
Did you take my body, like I said?
I always loved hearing you talk \Nabout your dreams, Denji.
Here's the deal. I'll give you my heart...
And in exchange, I want you \Nto show me your dream.
Pochita?!
I'm not hurt?
Pochita...?
What is this?
You're alive after being sliced up?
Why? Gross!
I seriously hate devil hunters.
Guys, go ahead and eat him.
These guys had plenty already, \Nso why'd they want even more?
Am I the same?
I wasn't satisfied with \Nthe happiness I had with Pochita.
I kept dreaming about a better life.
I guess we all dream \Nabout stuff like that, huh?
I can't blame you, then.
And I won't, but...
If you get in our way?
You'll die!
He's bound to stay dead after being eaten.
What are you?!
Did that devil runt take your body?!
That means you're one of us!
Ow...
It hurts!
Stay away!
Move!
Stay back! Back! Get away!
Stay away! Don't do it!
Don't come near me!
Die!
I guess you guys went full devil, huh?
Well, you hired me to be a devil hunter.
So, I better kill all the devils, right?!
Oh, yeah!
Once you're all dead...
I won't owe a damn thing!
Someone got here before us.
There's still one alive.
You've got a strange smell.
Not like a human or a devil.
I take it you did this?
H-Hug me...
He's human.
Any chance he's possessed?
No.
I can tell who's possessed \Nwith a look at their face.
I came here to kill the Zombie Devil.
I'm a devil hunter with Public Safety.
You have two options:
I can kill you like a devil,
or I can keep you as a human.
If I keep you, I'll make sure you're fed.
When you say that...
Like, what's for breakfast?
Bread with butter and jam, salad, coffee...
And then maybe something \Nfor dessert, I think?
That sounds awesome.
My view cracks as I see the rat race rush by
Flat on the ground looking up, \Nno matter how it makes me feel
The beat pounds in time, no clapping needed
So mad I wanna forget, \Nwith my chain spinning
The roar of my engine \Nis enough to drown it all out
And with a click of the tongue
Everything goes black with dried
CHAINSAW BLOOD
My blood can seethe or rage
But I just can't quit
No matter how I get smashed up, \Nthere's no stopping now
Whoo Whoo Whoo Whoo
Tell me why you cry?
Tell me why...?
CHAINSAW BLOOD
My blood can seethe or rage
But I just can't quit
Every blood of drop that \Ngoes down is a nightmare
Reborn
Whoo Whoo Whoo Whoo
Tell me why you cry?
Tell me why…?
CHAINSAW BLOOD
The blood can seethe or rage
But I just can't quit
Every blood of drop that \Ngoes down is a nightmare
Reborn
Whoo Whoo Whoo Whoo
Tell me why you cry...?
Tell me why... are you grinning?
That was my stomach.
What's your name?
It's Denji!
I need to tell you something right now.
From now on, you're in my care, Denji.
I expect "yes" or "woof" for answers. \NI don't need a dog that says "no."
When you say that...
Someone in forensics once told me...
That when we get dogs that \Naren't helpful, we put them down.
I thought she was nice.
I kind of liked her.
I had no idea she was scary like this.
Treating me like a damn dog...
I just remembered how Pochita's dead.
General
We haven't had breakfast yet, either. \NLet's grab something at the rest area.
Sorry, but I don't have any cash.
Just pick what you want. I'll pay.
And you're conspicuous \Nwithout a shirt on, so wear this.
Here.
All my life people have avoided me, \Nsaying I'm filthy and smell bad.
No one's ever been nice to me before.
Much less a girl who looks this good!
I love her!
I'll take some udon...
Udon and... a sausage!
Is that cool?
Sure is. I'll take a curry udon, please.
Coming up.
Oh, that sounds good, too...
Whoa, there.
Denji? You okay?
You smell good.
How much will it be?
Gimme one sec...
Denji?
It'll be 1,100 yen, all together.
The chainsaws cut me up, too,
Here's 2,000.
so I think I'm a little \Nlow on blood right now.
How did you end up like this?
I had a pet devil, and he replaced my heart.
Kinda hard to believe, huh?
I don't really wanna believe it, either.
Pochita dying for my sake...
There's not a lot of precedent \Nfor your condition,
even from a historical perspective.
It doesn't even have a name.
I believe you.
I've got a particularly good sense of smell.
So I can tell.
Your best friend is alive inside of you.
Not in the sentimental sense, either.
Your body has the scents \Nof both a human and a devil.
Is that right?
That's awesome!
Really... awesome...
Udon?!
The udon?
Is it cool if I eat my udon?
Are you all right? \NCan you eat on your own?
I can...
I can not.
Here. Say, "Ahh."
Ahh...
Is it good?
Woof!
You are really sweet to be \Nenjoying soggy udon this much.
A lot like a dog, actually.
Um... what's your name?
Makima.
Miss Makima... is there a type\N of guy you l-like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
Denji?
Dude, that's me.
Is there a type of guy you like?
I'm into the "Denji" type.
I like you, too, Miss Makima.
Denji? This way, come on.
This is the Tokyo headquarters \Nfor our Devil Hunters.
There are over a thousand Devil Hunters \Nin Tokyo, including civilians,
but Public Safety has the best benefits \Nand a lot of paid vacation time.
If Miss Makima likes me...
Then maybe, if we work together, \Nwe'll eventually get together?
And if we get together... \Nwe can get together, right?
I wanna! I wanna get together \Nwith her real bad!
Denji...
Yeah?
We're supposed to \Nwear uniforms, so put this on.
Once you've changed, \NI'll introduce you to a coworker.
This is Aki Hayakawa. He started \Nthree years before you, Denji.
You're going to be shadowing him today.
I'm not working with you, Miss Makima?
That should be obvious.
You're not even in her league.
Time for patrol.
No! Miss Makima!
Damn it, get up.
No way! I wanna work with Miss Makima!
If you do a good job, \Nwe can work together someday.
So, do that, okay?
Hey, big man.
Does Miss Makima have a boyfriend?
Hey, come on.
Hey!
Come with me.
You need to quit this job.
Show up tomorrow, \Nand I'll kick your ass again.
Why, though?
Look, I'm trying to be nice, here.
People who start this job without \Nthinking it through end up dead.
I've had colleagues who got \Ninto devil hunting for the payday,
and it got them all killed by devils.
The survivors are the ones \Nwith real motivation.
You're just after Makima, right? \NThat's why you took the job?
Ding-ding!
Then I'm glad I hit you.
I'll let her know that you ran off, \Nscared away by the devils.
You really are a nice guy, huh?
Because... when I fight a dude...
It's nuts... or nothing!
I had udon for the first time today, man.
A sausage, too.
Got treated like a decent \Nhuman being for the first time,
and even had someone pay for my meal.
It's like a dream come true for me.
I didn't really think it through \Nwhen I started devil hunting,
but if I get to keep up this kind of life?
I don't care if it kills me.
Actually, y'know, I take it back.
It's not just my life, anymore.
Makima...
is not the kind of woman \Na punk like you should be chasing!
What the hell are you saying?
Sounds to me like you just like her, too!
You... really did...
Only aim... for my balls...
Shit.
The big guy's testicles were attacked \Nby the Nut Devil, ma'am!
That's a lie. He's lying.
So, do you think you two can work together?
No way!
He's a piece of trash!
I'm glad you two are hitting it off.
Denji, you're going to \Nbe joining Hayakawa's unit.
Unit?
This punk?!
I've already got enough \Ntroublemakers, don't I?
Adding another... I don't know...
I told you when I put it together, right?
Your team's an experimental one, \Noperating differently from the usual method.
What exactly is he, ma'am?
Denji's human, but can \Ntransform into a devil.
Damn right! Pretty sweet, huh?
And that's the truth?
I always figured those stories \Nwere baseless rumors.
He's special.
Which is why he's going to be \Nreceiving special treatment.
If he tries to resign, \Nor becomes insubordinate...
Denji will be disposed of as a devil.
Uh, what's that mean?
It means we're working \Ntogether until you die.
You're going to be living with me \Nso I can keep an eye on you.
Just remember, they said I can \Nkill you if you try to run off.
Hey, is Miss Makima a bad person?
If you think that's the case, \Nthen give up on her.
If you're really a devil, you should \Njust be grateful she doesn't kill you.
We're Devil Hunters, got that?
So, she's a good person, then?
Of course she is.
She saved my life.
Miss Makima...
I hope I get to hug her again.
Strawberry jam, plum jam, orange jam...
Then some butter and honey, plus...
Let's throw some cinnamon on, too.
I got the best toast ever right here!
So good!
It's freaking fantastic!
How long are you gonna be in there?!
Don't fall asleep on the toilet!
A Fiend has been reported \Nin an east Nerima residence.
Civilian evacuation and cordon \Nare both complete.
The Fiend in question has \Nholed up in a second story room.
We'll leave it to you \NDevil Hunters from here.
Is this a new rookie, Hayakawa?
Hey, what's a Fiend?
Did you never go to school or something?
Nah, man, no.
When a devil takes control \Nof a human corpse, you get a Fiend.
Wait, doesn't that make me a Fiend?
No. Fiends always have characteristic heads.
Should be obvious enough once we see him.
The devil controls a Fiend's personality.\N You kill this one.
Turn into a devil, \Nand show me what you can do.
That'll help me figure out \Nif you're of any use.
Don't look at me...
You're dead! Dead, dead, dead!
Damn Devil Hunters!
Hey. Why didn't you use your devil powers?
Thing is...
When I kill devils with my powers, \Nthey get real messed up.
So, like... I coulda ended up \Nlike this Fiend, right?
So I kinda... wanted to \Nmake it painless for him.
All right. Listen to me.
Fiends are just like any other devil.
If you're hunting them, \Nthen drop the sympathy.
My entire family was killed \Nby a devil right in front of me.
I've had drinks with the cops down below.
They're risking their lives \Nto protect their wives and kids.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
I'd rather make any devil I kill \Nsuffer as much as possible.
What are you trying to do? \NMake friends with them?
If there's a devil I could be \Nfriends with, then yeah, I would.
'Cuz I don't have any friends.
I'll remember that.
Guess I pissed him off...
I was just trying to keep \Nblood off these dirty magazines.
When the chainsaws are out, blood gets \Neverywhere and makes a real mess.
I made it easy for you, \Nso I get to keep these!
Okay, the porn is secured.
I want you to show me your dream.
I'm pretty serious about this, Pochita.
I'm already living the dream, \Njust like our bargain said.
I'll remember that.
My dream might've come true already, \Nbut he must be chasing his.
I get to bathe every day, eat good food...
Get to hang around a hot chick...
My life's a 10 outta 10, but it feels \Nlike something's missing.
Am I missing something? Something that'd\N give me a real perfect score?
He's gotta be after some revenge shit.
They're trying to protect their families.
I wonder if Miss Makima \Nis after anything like that?
Miss Makima...
I wanna touch her boobs.
Touching boobs is a dream I gave\N up on a long time ago,
but I've got a real job now. \NMaybe I could pull it off?
I probably couldn't score \Nwith a girl just yet.
But boobs?
If I had the right plan, and the\N willpower, then maybe...
Everyone is serious about this except you.
So that's what he meant!
I've found it! Something to be serious about!
My goal! It's...
Boobs!
Boobs?
Hey! Pay attention, dumbass!
Listen to what?
I'm assigning you a partner \Nstarting today, Denji.
Partner?
As a precaution, Public Safety executes patrols
and smaller missions with two-person teams.
This is great timing. She's here.
Be careful. She's a Fiend.
Prostrate yourselves, humans!
For I am Power!
Are you to be my so-called partner?!
Power?! Your name's Power?!
And you're a Fiend?!
Are Fiends allowed to be Devil Hunters?!
Well, whatever! Nice to meet you!
Fiends, like devils, \Nare targets for extermination.
But Power's highly rational,
so she's been on Hayakawa's team.
I mentioned this before,
but Public Safety Devil Extermination \NSpecial Division 4 is an experimental unit.
The higher-ups will be looking \Nto dissolve your team as soon as possible
if you can't get results.
I don't need to explain what would happen \Nto you two if that happens, do I?
Power's horns stand out a bit too much,
so you'll want to patrol areas \Nwithout a lot of pedestrians.
Human! Provide me with something \Nto kill immediately!
I am starved for blood!
I can put up with crazy, \Nas long as she's hot enough.
The question is, how do I get \Nmy hands on those boobs?
If you run into any civilian Devil Hunters,
or the police try to question you \Nabout what you're doing...
We've got a pair of suspicious individuals...
Excuse me, I need to ask you—
We're with Public Safety Devil \NExtermination Special Division 4.
...say that, show them your ID,
and they'll make a sour face \Nand leave you alone.
Where the hell are all the devils?!
This is likely my fault!
Before becoming a Fiend, \NI was a devil that was feared by all!
Demonic peons will likely flee \Nthe moment they catch my scent!
Wait, how are we gonna \Nget anything done, then?!
If you have any questions, \Njust ask Hayakawa.
He's the one who put you two together.
That asshole! He set me up!
He stuck me with Power \Nso I can't do anything cool!
He's trying to get me fired!
The scent of blood!
Whoa! Hey, crazy, where you going?!
The game is afoot!
The battle is joined!
Damn, she's fast!
The scene's evacuated and blocked off.
It's the Sea Cucumber Devil. \NYes, the Sea Cucumber Devil.
Requesting backup \Nin front of Nerima Station.
I said, it's the Sea Cucumber—
Do you know what a sea cucumber is?
Look, I'm trying to say—
What the...?
Did you see?! The kill is mine!
If Public Safety kills \Na civilian hunter's devil,
we're guilty of obstructing their business.
Normally, you'd be arrested \Nfor that kind of thing.
Power, you're going to need \Nto think a bit more before acting.
And you'll have to get her \Nunder control, Denji.
I'm in trouble, too?
Before becoming a Fiend, \NPower was the Blood Devil...
So she's got a talent \Nfor using blood in battle,
but also gets worked up pretty easily.
Maybe she's not cut out to be \Na Devil Hunter after all.
It...
I-It was he who commanded me to kill!
I did not! How can you just lie like that?!
It is no lie! It was him!
The human ordered me to kill \Nthis devil! That's the truth!
What a creep!
Miss Makima, this devil's a total liar!
You oughta arrest her right now!
You're under arrest for the crime \Nof being a fake-ass liar!
Not true! It was by his command!
Devils do not lie! It is only humans who do!
No one ever said that!
And you're the reason why! \NDumbass! Shitty liar!
Humans and your filthy lies!
I only did as I was told!
Why the hell do you talk like \Nthat anyway?! It's so creepy!
Could you quiet down?
Y-Yes.
Very good, Power.
Honestly, I don't really care \Nwho got in whose way.
I want to see the two of you \Nworking well together.
Can you show me that?
We... W-We can.
Maybe I should worry about \Ncopping a feel some other time.
Y'know, being able to just grab a drink \Nlike this is a dream come true to me.
But if we keep screwing up,
being thirsty is probably gonna be \Nthe least of my problems.
Not that it'll make it any easier to work \Nwith some chick that lies, though.
I only enjoy the company of cats.
I hate humans.
It's not a matter of personal grievance.
My hatred is almost like a demonic instinct.
And I hate devils, too.
Since one of them took \Nmy pet Meowy away.
Before I was able to recover Meowy, \NI fell into Makima's clutches.
My dear Meowy may be dead already, and yet...\NI find it hard to give up hope.
If it lets me retrieve Meowy \Nfrom that demon,
I'm willing to abide humans, \Nor anything else I needs must.
I doubt you'd understand \Nsuch concern for a cat.
For a cat? That's dumb as hell.
But I'd do whatever it takes \Nto get to fondle some boobs.
It seems I may never understand humans.
But I think I'd get you if it was a dog.
What would you say to the \Nprospect of fondling my chest
after retrieving Meowy from that devil?
That fucking devil...
thinks he can just kidnap some poor cat?!
Well, I don't think so!
As a Devil Hunter, I say no!
I'm gonna kill the shit out of that devil!
Leave for the Fiend, Power, is approved.
Make sure to have her back by 5:00 PM.
You're not even allowed to \Ngo out on your own?
Indeed. I've had to idly while \Naway my time in here.
I know where the devil \Nthat kidnapped Meowy dwells.
The concern is that you are \Nthe only one who can fight it.
He's likely to use Meowy \Nas a shield upon seeing me.
If that happens, then all is lost.
I had a pet devil named Pochita, y'know?
I can't pet him anymore, but it's cool.
Because he's alive in here.
How foolish you humans are.
Does that not mean Pochita is dead?
Death is the absence of life. \NThis nonsense about living on in your heart
is little more than miserable self-comfort.
Uh-huh. I guess so.
I don't think I'm ever \Ngonna get along with her.
The American matter has got the Soviet \Nwar hawks crowing more loudly than ever.
There are rumors about \Nthe military use of devils, as well.
Hopefully, devils will remain \NJapan's only enemies in the future.
Makima, how are the hunting dogs
that have been added \Nto the squad performing?
There's one that seems promising, \Nand another that seems interesting.
Interesting...?
A pup that I just recently picked up.
Your job is to raise these hounds, \Nand then put them to work.
Make sure not to grow attached.
As far as I can tell, \NDenji's disgusting, not "interesting."
Why do you have such high hopes for him?
All devils are born with names.
And the more those names are feared,
the more powerful the devil \Nis said to become.
Coffee isn't considered very frightening,
so a Coffee Devil would probably be weak.
But what about a Car Devil?
It's easy to imagine being run over \Nand dying, so it would probably be strong.
And Denji can turn into a Chainsaw Devil.
Seems pretty interesting to me.
He might be interesting, \Nbut I'm not sure he'll be any use.
Everyone in Public Safety has \Na real goal or motivation.
But he said he just wants \Nto live the good life.
He's a bad fit for our operation.
Not only that, but he thinks \Nhe can be friends with devils.
He's still a kid. A stupid brat.
That is the house!
Meowy and the devil are in there.
Well, we better get going, then.
Hope I don't have to chainsaw out. \NLosing all that blood's a drag.
Chainsaw?
Yeah. I can turn into a buncha chainsaws.
Human jokes leave much to be desired.
What is it now?
Isn't he gonna use the cat \Nas a hostage if he sees you?
Should you even, like, be this close?
Oh, I did say that, didn't I?
You said...?
I misspoke.
Fool that you are, it seems \Nyour instincts are sharp.
You kept me waiting \Na long time, Blood Devil.
I thought you had run away.
Spare me your complaints! \NIt took me this long to gain some freedom.
And I've brought a human \Njust as you demanded, Bat!
My first meal in ages...
A young man? I'm sure his \Nblood will be full of vigor.
Look at my arm, human.
The wound that your kind gave me!
The damnable wound \Nthat forced me into hiding!
Like I give a shit. Dumbass.
Food shouldn't speak!
Time to heal the wounds humans \Ngave me with human blood!
Disgusting!
I've been revived with awful-tasting blood!
The inside of my mouth tastes disgusting...
I need to cleanse my palate \Nwith another human now!
What are you trying to do? \NMake friends with them?
I'm amazed you actually believed my story.
Humans truly are foolish.
The stench of cigarettes...
The scent of makeup and drugs...
Are you serious?
Wow!
There's a decent aroma.
I'll cleanse my palate with some children.
Bat Devil!
I brought you a human, as promised!
Release Meowy.
Oh, I did say I'd do that, didn't I?
Meowy!
But I hadn't punished you for bringing me \Nsuch nasty blood yet, had I?
Meowy...?
Meowy!
Your name shall be Meowy!
You smell tasty, for a cat.
So spindly, though.
Let's put some meat \Non those bones before I feast.
Grow big and strong, now.
I'm looking forward to killing you, Meowy.
I've killed all who've met my eyes.
It's become strange to hear a voice \Nthat isn't screaming.
So strange...
Blood Devil...
I need blood.
If you want to save this cat, \Nthen bring me a human.
You said you couldn't pet \NPochita anymore, yes?
I understand how you feel now.
'Tis an awful feeling.
Nasty!
All of this repulsive blood!
The inside of my mouth feels filthy!
I need to gargle with the blood of children!
After I gargle, a virgin \Nshould make a fine appetizer.
Then a beefy man for a main course...
And a pregnant woman for dessert.
Gimme my tits back!
You're drinking my blood?! \NThat's disgusting!
I don't even feel like drinking your blood!
There was a time I couldn't find Pochita.
He was gone when I woke up in the morning...
So I looked all over town, \Nbut couldn't find him.
I thought a devil might've eaten him,
but when I got home, \Nhe was crying, waiting for me.
I remember being so relieved, \NI fell asleep holding him.
I wonder how she felt when she tried to sleep,\Nknowing that devil had Meowy.
You're a devil?!
Hey, dumbass! You wanna get eaten?!
You let her escape?
You're a devil! \NWhat do you think you're doing?!
Think I'm gonna split open your guts...
And then cop me a feel!
Get out of here already!
If you're so set on saving humans...
Can you cut through this?!
The chainsaws retract?!
Such brute strength in that tiny body!
Why would you use that power \Nto save a human?!
You think I saved him?
Western Tokyo
I don't give a shit...
about saving some dude!
I need to heal now.
Your blood reeks of cigarettes, \Nbut it should do, for now.
How are you still alive?!
Through all of this crap...
I've been about as patient as possible.
So how come I haven't...
gotten to cop a single damn feel yet?!
S-Stay away!