If you want to save this cat, \Nthen bring me a human.
One life is worth as little as any other.
And this is only a cat.
So why do I run? \NWhy do I search for a human?
Is it to save Meowy?
Such a foolish reason.
I love blood.
The taste, the smell, \Nthe sense of mortality...
And then... there is something \NI only recently realized:
The blood is warm...
And feels pleasant.
Why did you save me?
I attempted to kill you.
Such a foolish reason.
Forgive my deceit.
Since Meowy is safe...
You may fondle my chest.
Hell yeah!
Holy shit! Ow!
That hurts!
Can you move?
Not even a finger.
Take Meowy and flee, please.
Damn it, not enough chainsaw...
I must be low on blood.
And after I finally found him...
It's you, right? The one who killed Batty.
He was my man, y'know?!
Oh... but you're actually \Npretty cute yourself.
You're my type, so I'll let you go!
What about them?
They die.
Then you can die, too.
He can fight so fiercely...
To merely fondle a chest?
Is this a joke?
How'd a little pupper \Nlike you kill my Batty?
Y'know, he and I shared a dream: \Nkilling and eating all of humanity.
A pipe dream, but a noble one, \Nand a romantic one.
And now this little \Nyipping dog has ruined it.
You're cute enough that I regret it...
But you still need to die.
I'm not dying before I cop a feel.
That is ridiculous!
To think he was killed by someone \Nwith such a trashy dream.
Alas, poor Batty...
Such a foolish reason.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
Everybody wants to trash-talk my plans...
It's revenge this,
protect my family that,
and save a cat, too!
Blah, blah, blah!
I guess your fancy dreams \Nmake you guys hot shit, huh?!
How about we have us a dream battle, then?! \NHow about that?!
If I murderize you,
that means your dream's \Nweaker than fondling a tit!
Even your howls are cute!
But y'know what they say about \Nlittle dogs barking! Yap, yap, yap!
Okay! I'll gobble you up, then!
Go ahead...
If you can beat me in the dream battle!
Demoniacal...
Time to eat...
Kon.
Huh... Huh?
Looks like she's the Leech Devil. \NMay I swallow?
Do it.
The Leech Devil's extermination is confirmed.
I want the rookies handling search \Nand rescue, plus assisting with the evac.
Yes, sir!
Himeno, you've got seniority, \Nso keep watch for more devils.
On it.
Dream battle... Gonna... My dream battle...
You and the Blood Fiend \Nneed to be debriefed.
And Meowy?
Have the cat sent to a veterinarian \Nfor a thorough checkup.
I found your arm.
A blood infusion was all \Nit needed to reattach.
You really are like a devil.
You seemed pretty friendly \Nwith that devil back there.
I saw.
You really don't know a thing, huh?
Devil Hunters form contracts with \Ndevils in order to fight against them.
I've got a contract with the Fox Devil.
In exchange for power, \NI offer up a bit of my body as food.
It was some skin this time.
Sounds painful.
Devils yearn for the deaths of humans.
The same goes for Fiends.
Power seems cool, though.
The surveillance cameras caught \Nyou two headed to your patrol area.
Paused
And the house that we believe \Nwas housing the Bat Devil
contained a lot of your spilt blood.
The Blood Fiend tried to kill you, didn't she?
I don't know why, but you're trying \Nto protect a devil. Again.
I dunno... is that how it happened?
My daughter would like \Nto meet the chainsaw guy.
Thank you.
The devil threatened to eat \Nme back at the office,
but now that I think about it, he was \Nwearing a Public Safety uniform.
I'd like to thank him.
"Don't give a shit about \Nsaving some dude," he says!
And then the devil throws \Nmy car with me in it!
It was a devil with a chainsaw \Ncoming out of its head...
If I dig deeper into this, \Nand report it to the higher-ups,
it'd mean the Blood Fiend gets disposed of\N along with you, since you covered for her.
But there were no fatalities.
So, if you're willing to accept one condition, \NI'll let what happened slide.
You need to do what I tell you to.
You're a dumbass and a brat \Nwith no clue about right and wrong.
I've been doing this longer, so I'm pretty\N sure I have some grasp of social ethics.
All you need to do to protect \Nthis lifestyle is listen to me.
How about it? If you follow, \NI want an answer.
Sure. I'll keep it in mind.
You can relax.
I might not be after some \Nbig-deal goal like you guys,
and I might dream small.
But I'm as serious about this as you are.
You can count on me.
Try and learn some manners in the meantime.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
You see? Am I not innocent?
Now, would you kindly take these off?
Is this a good idea?
When this cutie-Fiend kills somebody,
it's gonna be your responsibility, \Nfor letting her live.
We're Devil Hunters.
Whether they're devils or Fiends,
if they're handy, \Nwe should put them to work.
But they're still the enemy. \NWe're just making use of them.
We're not making friends.
Come in.
Excuse me.
And he claims they "were outside \Nthe patrol zone before they knew it,"
and that they discovered a house that\N"looked like it had a super-nasty devil in it,"
which is where they encountered \Nthe Bat Devil.
Denji used his chainsaws to\N exterminate the Bat Devil,
and then came under attack \Nby the Leech Devil...
Which Division 4 exterminated.
There were no traces of Gun flesh \Nin either the Bat or Leech Devil's heads.
That concludes my report.
Well done.
But Denji and Power managed to get awfully \Nfar without anyone noticing, didn't they?
I'd chalk that up to them \Nbeing unbelievably stupid.
Leaving the approved area \Nis against regulations.
Considering there were no fatalities,
and that we were able to get rid of \Ntwo devils, I think it's worth overlooking.
Understood.
If you'll excuse me, ma'am.
You seem a little more \Nflexible now, Hayakawa.
Is that Denji's influence, I wonder?
I doubt it.
I haven't changed at all.
How's he up so early?
What's for lunch?
Curry.
Sweet!
The hell's this? A devil?
What a pitiful home this is!
I'd like you to put Power up \Nin one of your rooms, Hayakawa.
I think you'll make a good leash \Nfor the two of them.
Stop right there, Meowy!
It seems you've got quite a feast!
Damn it, who said you could come in?!
'Tis mine now!
Gimme my super toast back!
Oh... okay.
It'd be a little odd to have her \Nstaying at the office indefinitely.
Okay.
You don't need to worry. \NPower said she would behave.
It'll be fine.
Vegetables are revolting!
Away!
Carrot!
Don't fling your vegetables!
Damn it...
Show some respect to the farmers \Nwho grew the veggies, devil!
The toilet?
I prefer to only occasionally \Nflush my feces.
Flush it!
It stinks.
I prefer to only occasionally bathe.
Get in there!
You reek!
You two are absurd.
How delicate these humans be.
Aren't they, Meowy?
Can't believe she just shows up \Nand starts raising hell.
Do devils not flush the toilet?
Didn't eat her veggies either.
You there...
Hey, Shit Devil! Your turds are stuck \Nto the damn toilet and won't come off!
We had a deal, did we not?
You may fondle my chest.
So, fondle!
Come now, what's the matter? \NAren't you pleased?
Commence your fondling.
I have stipulations, however.
You have earned three squeezes of my breast.
Three?
One for your rescue of Meowy.
A second for slaying the Bat Devil.
And a third for protecting me from topknot!
I had no intention of actually letting you,
but your efforts have earned \Nyou these three squeezes.
Squeeze them gratefully.
She's an angel!
BLAAAARGH!
Lalalalah
Denji,\NHear\NMe\NOut
It feels so good!
What the...?
Breast pads.
A wondrous invention that \Nmakes your bosom look bigger.
Now! Two squeezes remain.
And now! The final fondling!
There, done! All done!
What did you think? Was it not fantastic?
How lucky for you, to grasp \Nsuch splendorous things!
And now we are even!
With Meowy saved, I have no real reason \Nto hunt devils any longer,
There's lots of stuff I could say, but... Huh?
yet there's no escaping Makima!
So I will aid you all with your duty!
I'm sure the pleasure is all yours!
Meowy! Off to bed we go!
That's it?
This is good!
Seconds would be splendid!
I'll eat yours, if you won't have it!
You little...!
Where shall we slaughter devils today?
Hey.
Hey!
Chop!
This is the form apology \Nfor the damage to the buildings.
This is for verifying \Nthe disposal of the devils' bodies.
Then there's this, from the Ministry of Land, \NInfrastructure, Transport and Tourism.
You'll need to stamp it, here and here.
I hate making you do all this paperwork.
It's almost like killing \Nthe Bat Devil was a bad thing.
Is something bothering you, Denji?
Y'know, I...
There's something I was chasing after, \Nand I finally managed to get it.
But once I did, it wasn't...
as big of a deal as I thought.
Now I'm wondering, if I go after \Nsomething else, and get my hands on it,
am I just gonna think \NI was happier during the chase?
That's, like... total bullshit, isn't it?
What exactly are you talking about, Denji?
I touched boobs for the first time,\N but it wasn't that great.
Denji...
I believe that, when it comes to sex,
the better you understand \Nthe other person, the better it feels.
But it's hard to understand \Nhow someone else feels.
So, start with observing \Nthe hand, carefully.
How long are their fingers?
Are their palms cold?
Are they warm?
What's the shape of their ears?
Ever had your finger bitten?
B-Bit...?
Remember this.
So that even if you can't see,
you'll be able to tell it's me, \Nfrom how hard I'm biting.
Memorize it.
I... got it.
Denji...
I'd like to ask you to do something for me.
Can I?
Yeah.
I want you to beat the Gun Devil.
Gun Devil?
It appeared in America 13 years ago, \Nbut nobody knows where it is now.
It's a very strong devil \Nthat all hunters want to kill.
But I happen to think that you can kill it.
Because you're not like any \Nof the other Devil Hunters.
And if you're able to kill the Gun Devil,
I'll make any wish of yours come true.
You're saying if your Denji\N kills the Gun Devil,
Miss Makima's gonna make \Nany wish of his come true?
So... like, I mean...
You're saying if your Denji\N kills the Gun Devil,
Miss Makima's gonna make \Nany wish of his come true?
Anything, like... even se—
I said anything, Denji.
Holy shit! Is that even allowed?!
It's only allowed because this devil \Nis so strong and bad, mind you.
People were trying to profit off of guns
as a counter-measure against \Ndevils across the world,
which resulted in an increase \Nin crime and conflict.
The news focused on it \Nnon-stop for a while,
with people more afraid \Nof gun violence than ever.
Then a major armed terrorist \Nattack happened in America.
That was the day the Gun Devil appeared.
"This is where I live," said the city mouse.
The Country Mouse and the City Mouse
And, oh what a big house it was!
The city mouse's family—
Dad!
Let's play catch outside.
Taiyo doesn't feel well. \NFind something you can play by yourself.
He never does.
I don't remember him feeling good.
You're the older brother. \NBe good and play by yourself.
I...
I wanna play with him.
Quit following me.
You're so annoying... I said cut it out!
I'm gonna play by myself.
Gotcha!
Stupid! I said cut it out!
It's cold...
If you catch a cold, \NI'm gonna get in trouble.
Your hands won't get cold \Nif we play catch, right?
Go grab a glove from the house.
Yes!
In a little under five minutes, \N1.2 million people were killed.
The Gun Devil hasn't been seen since.
Fear of devils across the board \Nincreased as a result,
making them all stronger than ever before.
Gun control got a lot more severe \Nin an attempt to weaken the Gun Devil...
Along with increased censorship of the news.
I'm not sure I understand, but...
Let's say this thing's so strong, \Nit's hard to understand.
Do you think you can beat it, Denji?
Well... I'd say...
If I bust out all the stops,
it'll be a peace of cake.
In that case...
First, we'll need to actually \Nfind the Gun Devil.
How exactly are we gonna do that, anyway?
These are pieces of the Gun Devil \Nthat we've collected.
It's so fast, pieces of it \Nare torn off just from moving.
If a devil eats some of this,
no matter what their nature, \Nthey become more powerful.
See how they stick together?
Because of how powerful the Gun Devil is,
once the chunks of flesh \Nreach a certain size,
they start to be attracted \Nto the original body.
So if we can make this piece bigger,
it'll lead us to the Gun Devil.
Got one.
So it really was snacking \Non a piece of the Gun.
Explains how such \Na wimpy devil got so strong.
But did it find that piece, \Nor did someone serve it up?
Doesn't change what our job is.
We keep killing devils,
and eventually, we'll find him.
Public Safety's received a request \Nfor devil extermination.
A devil has been spotted inside of a hotel.
No confirmation on the status \Nof the hotel's guests.
Several of the civilian devil hunters \Nwho initially went in have been found dead.
It's believed the target has \Nconsumed a piece of the Gun Devil.
We're sending six agents from Public Safety \NDevil Extermination Special Division 4.
It's hiding somewhere in this hotel.
And this is no ordinary devil.
It's eaten a piece of the Gun Devil's flesh.
Maybe it's the Gun Devil for real?
The more flesh, the stronger the attraction. \NThe reaction's not big enough.
Huh, guess not.
How amusing... Give that thing to me!
I thought I told you two \Nto work on your manners.
Who the hell's gonna suck up \Nto you for no reason?
How foolish and conceited these humans be!
Mr. Hayakawa.
Sir.
Good.
Sweet!
Dude, he's so easy.
Hayakawa!
Considering we're about \Nto fight some devils...
Can we really trust these two \Nto watch our backs?
One's a Fiend, and the other is some punk...
I'm not sure about this.
We can't let them watch our backs.
On extermination missions, \Nthey'll be taking point.
If they try to run \Nor switch sides, we kill them.
You're treating us like livestock!
You two don't get rights.
He's super pissed.
Must be from this morning.
Perhaps our prank went too far?
You call that a prank?! I could kill you!
Yikes! What happened?
Aki, you can't just be harsh \Nall the time, y'know?
She's right! The bat almost killed me, \Nand now there's more work?!
I want a reward!
Got it! I'll take one for the team.
Whoever kills this devil will win...
a kiss on the cheek from yours truly!
That's... You shouldn't do that!
A young woman who's not married \Nshouldn't be so... indecent!
But doesn't a reward help with motivation?
Right?
I'm not gonna sweat the kisses.
Don't worry about it. I'm plenty motivated.
Oh?
I got my sights set on someone \Nfor a first kiss already.
I'm gonna find all these meat chunks \Nor whatever for her.
So, until the Gun Devil's dead, \Nno smooching for me.
That's a hell of a thing \Nto say in front of Aki!
Besides, I learned something real important.
Sex stuff feels better when it's \Ntwo people who get each other.
I don't even know your name, \Nso I ain't after your lips!
Then, if you kill the devil, Denji...
I'll give you a kiss... with tongue.
Hey, hold it!
It's dangerous to run off solo! Stop!
th Floor
Damn, I love teasing boys!
Oh man, what are we gonna do?
I yearn for blood.
It's dangerous! You need to stop!
Himeno's been nice enough to train me \Nfor the last six months!
If the alternative is letting \Nsome thug like you kiss her...
Then I'll take that kiss on the cheek!
Move!
I don't want some dude \Nall over me! It's nasty!
Say what?!
Die! I'm after a way \Nbigger goal than you, dude!
I wish to join you!
Shut up! I don't wanna hear that \Nfrom someone newer than me!
What's your take on the rookies, Himeno?
Man, shut up!
More of this! Yes!
I'd say Arai's not super competent, \Nbut makes up for it in motivation.
Get him, get him!
Meanwhile, Kobeni's got the moves, \Nbut she's really timid.
You think any of the four rookies \Nhave a shot of surviving, Aki?
It's a duel to the death!
You get the picture, now?
regardless of how strong \NI thought they were.
You are not kissing Himeno!
Asshole... I'm gonna kill you!
That's not really an answer.
Power... you're dead, too!
You too, shorty.
But why?!
Himeno...
This is your new partner.
He's rude, but I trained him \Nto be of some use.
Try and get along.
I'm Aki.
Nice to meet you.
Are you gonna be any help?
Well... I think so.
You're gonna be my sixth partner.
The others all died.
They all died because they were useless.
Don't die on me, Aki.
Gotta say, I'm not seeing \Nany devils around here.
Does that meat chunk of yours even work?
So tired...
Aki...
Incoming.
Got it.
It floats?!
The battle is joined!
Damnable devil! Did you see \Nhow it floated in fear of me?!
No, no, that's my power.
Say what?
I've got a contract with the Ghost Devil.
I served up my right eye in exchange \Nfor being able to use a ghost's right hand.
My ghost hand's invisible \Nand strong. Pretty slick, right?
How about it, Aki? \NHas he got any of the Gun's flesh?
No strong reaction. This isn't the one.
I see... guess we better keep heading up.
Is it wise to blather on about \Nyour powers in my presence?
Are you people not meant to hold my reins?
Knowing about our powers makes \Nfor better teamwork, right?
Besides, I've got a few tricks \Nup my sleeve, so I'm not worried.
Truly?
So what would you do if I said \NI was going to kill this one?
Put the weapon away.
If you misbehave, \NI can always choke you to death.
Can't... touch it...
I'd prefer if we got along. It's easier!
I will devour you in time!
You better not. I'm trying to get a kiss.
Do you guys not get that the devil \Nis still around? Can't you pipe...
Huh?
She does look like \Nshe'd be unpleasant raw.
What is it?
That sounds pervy, dude.
We were... on our way to \Nthe 9th floor from the 8th, right?
Perhaps boiling or frying...
Cook your own ass, stupid.
th Floor
But this is the 8th floor.
You probably read it wrong.
It's not that! Something's going on here!
I'm gonna double check.
I know! Grilled like a steak!
Steak?!
I wanna try steak!
Huh?
Arai... just now... you were \Ngoing downstairs, right?
{\blur3\fax-0.11\t(1,750,\blur0)\c&H10262F&\frz27.06\pos(345,123)\frx30\fry342\fs13}th Floor
Huh?
Arai... just now... you were \Ngoing downstairs, right?
Kobeni, make a double \Npeace sign and stay put.
Well, shit.
Aki... what's going on here?
It has to be a devil's power at work.
Kobeni, stand right there.
Why are there rooms \Non the other side of the window?
Hey! None of the windows go anywhere!
They just open to the room across the hall!
I figured as much.
We're trapped on the eighth floor.
th Floor
Let's run through what we know.
This is probably a devil's doing,
and no matter how many times \Nwe try to go to a different floor,
we end up on the eighth again.
The elevator is inoperable \Nfor whatever reason.
There's no way outside via \Nthe rooms or any windows.
We tried going through the ceiling, \Nbut ended up on the eighth floor again.
Maybe it's because Power killed that devil?
He coulda died while using \Nthe power to keep us trapped.
And now—
You commanded me to kill him!
Did not!
A devil's powers are released \Nwhen they die. It can't be that.
Is the flesh piece reacting, Aki?
Actually...
It's gone dead still.
That devil before was bait, and we bit hard.
I've never seen a devil try \Nsomething so clever before.
But if no one hears from us for a while,
won't other Devil Hunters \Nshow up to help?
I guess we better hope they don't fall \Ninto the same kind of trap, then.
We're all gonna die here.
We're gonna starve to death.
H-Hang in there, Kobeni!
Didn't you become a Devil Hunter \Nto send your brother to college?!
They basically forced me to do it.
My parents are set on my \Nolder brother going to college,
since he's the gifted one.
So they made me get a job.
It was become a Devil Hunter \Nor a sex worker!
I wanted to go to college, too!
And now I'm gonna die here!
Her face...!
Enough!
Quit laughing!
Kobeni, devils love fear, okay?
If you get scared, you're giving them \Nwhat they want, sweetie.
But I'm so scared!
Something bothering you, too, Aki?
The clocks in this room...
have been stuck at 8:18 for a while now.
In every single room... it's 8:18.
There's a chance that time has been \Nfrozen here on the eighth floor.
And if that's the case, no one is coming.
Oh, shit! Then we can sleep all we want, right?
How stupid are you?
We might be trapped in here forever.
I mean, we might be, but we\N might not be, too, y'know?
Wake me when you figure it out.
This bed is freaking sweet. \NIt'd be stupid not to sleep in it.
I owe the devil for this nap.
He's actually asleep...
Denji.
Rise and shine, Denji.
We find a way off the eighth floor yet?
Hate to break it to you, but not yet.
We found out the water and electricity \Nare still working while you were asleep.
There was a little bit of food that some of \Nthe guests who ran must've left behind.
I'll be honest, everyone's really worn out.
Aki's been searching \Nfor the devil nonstop.
I told him to take a break, \Nbut he won't listen.
Arai was helping Aki at first,
but now he's locked himself up in \Nanother room to have a panic attack.
Kobeni freaked out and tried to drink \Ntoilet bowl water, so I knocked her out.
And as for the Fiend...
Something happen to Power?
Given there's nothing else to do, \NI've decided to win the Nobel Prize!
Once I've earned such glorious esteem, \Nthe humans will all kowtow to me!
And with the Nobel Prize as my foothold,
I shall ascend to the prime minister's throne!
What better way to ensure human suffering?
My first act will be passing a 100% sales tax!
She's always like that.
Huh. Okay, then.
Let's take turns watching Kobeni and Arai.
I couldn't even use the bathroom \Nwhen it was just me.
Well, this is my last cigarette.
I'm bored by how little this upsets you.
I can take it easy because \NAki's working hard.
The nicotine also helps!
Gotta have a port in a storm, right?
Life is sweeter with a bit of dependence.
Hey, that's the same brand he smokes.
That's because Aki learned all \Nabout the flavor of cigarettes
from yours truly!
Not gonna smoke, Aki?
No. It's bad for your bones.
You should start. It's great for socializing.
I'm not looking to make friends.
Let me guess why you joined Public Safety.
You're out to kill the Gun Devil, right?
Everyone who signs up with a chip \Non their shoulder is the same...
since only Public Safety is allowed to hold\N onto pieces of the Gun Devil's flesh.
Devil Hunters die young anyway. \NMight as well smoke.
I don't plan on dying any time soon.
I'll hold you to that.
It's a pain in the ass \Nwhen your partner dies.
What the hell was that?
She was my old partner's girlfriend.
It happens a lot. You get issues with the\N family and friends of dead partners.
They can't do anything to get back \Nat the devils, so they take it out on me.
I just consider it something \Nthat comes with the territory.
What was that about?
I put gum on the clothes \Nof that girl who hit you.
You shouldn't just sit back \Nand take being treated like that.
No need for you to feel guilty. \NI was pissed off.
So I got some payback.
Serves her right.
She's gonna waltz around without realizing \Nthere's a wad of gum on her clothing.
There's something my master said...
Devils don't fear Devil Hunters\N who are strong or brave.
They fear Devil Hunters who have a screw loose.
Which is why I think you'll survive \Na long time in this job, Aki.
Was that an insult?
And I'll eat your almond tofu \Nif you don't want it.
Just one.
I'm not smoking. It's bad for your bones.
I wish you would. I get the feeling \Nwe're gonna be together for a while.
Just one, then.
This is the first and last \Ncigarette I ever light up.
Himeno, do you have any smokes left?
Sorry. Last one.
Let me have it, please.
If you insist...
Dude, that's kissing! No fair! \NThat's an indirect kiss!
Shut up.
I've got bad news.
Remember the devil we killed?
The one that I slew!
Well, he's a lot bigger now.
That really is the one I slew.
It traps us in a hotel... \Nand its body turns into that?
What the hell kind of devil is this?
Humans. Hear me, humans.
You foolish humans. \NI offer you a contract...
It talked!
A contract?
Feed me the human known as Denji.
Even his corpse will do.
Let me eat him.
Do this, and I'll let the rest \Nof you leave in peace.
You'll be free to leave! \NNow, accept this contract!
Do it... Do it...
Denji... let it eat you.
Man, that's obnoxious.
Aki, can't you swallow \Nthis thing with the Fox Devil?
Kon.
Looks like Fox Devil isn't coming.
We're cut off from the rest of the world.
The Fox Devil's body is in Kyoto, \Nso that makes sense.
Let's see what my Ghost can do, then.
That hurt!
It hurts! Oh, it hurts! The pain!
It hurts...! It hurts!
It got even bigger!
It's pointless!
This isn't my main body...
You won't find my heart here.
You're inside of my stomach...
and I have no weaknesses \Non this eighth floor.
There is no way to survive this place, \Napart from accepting my offer.
You're probably not gonna \Nlet them go, even if I do die.
Actually, no.
The devil used the word "contract," right?
Those kinds of terms hold a strong sway \Nwhen a devil is involved.
If one side makes good on the deal, \Nthe other has to or else.
Whichever side breaks \Nthe contract ends up dying.
So, we would be able to leave \Nby killing you, Denji.
Himeno... we should kill him.
We can come up with another plan \Nonce he's dead, and we're out of here.
We're all gonna end up starving otherwise.
Devil Hunters are legally allowed to \Nmake contracts with devils.
We should take the deal!
The devil wants Denji dead.
That means his death would benefit it,
which is why we're not accepting.
I'm with him!
But...
I say we kill him!
My Nobel Prize will remain forever out of \Nreach if I'm unable to leave this place!
You must die for my Nobel.
Fiends can't make pacts with devils.
It wouldn't be obligated to let us leave, \Neven if you killed him.
Look, we're not killing Denji. \NWe're Devil Hunters.
We only kill devils.
Shall we wrestle to pass the time, then?
You're just gonna try and kill me! Hell no!
So hungry...
Aki, have you got any kind of plan \Nfor actually getting us out of here?
If what the devil says \Nis true, we can't kill it.
But we're not killing Denji, either.
So, is the plan to starve, then?
If we really run out of options, \NI'll use the sword.
No, you won't.
If that thing can get us out of here,
shouldn't he use it?
He shouldn't use it, \Neven if we're out of options.
If it comes to that... sorry,
but you'll have to die, Denji!
It's gone?!
It's gone... all the food \Nthat was left on the bed...
None of it's left.
Why?
You ate all of it, didn't you?
'Twas not me. This is Denji's doing.
Of all the obvious lies...
I get it now...
I figured it out.
We can't get out of here because \Nof that Fiend's power!
That has to be it!
No, it doesn't.
Calm down, Kobeni! This is the Blood Fiend—
So you're taking her side? \NEven though we're Devil Hunters?!
You're on the devil's side, Arai!
You're a spy!
He's spycy.
I... I'm not on the devil's side...
I know you're a spy!
Was that a scream?
We need to move!
Kill Denji...
Give me his heart... Give it!
I will grow as your fear grows... \Nand with your terror, I will capture you!
So, fear me more!
Be overcome by your impending death!
Dread everything.
I will be the one to kill Chainsaw...
It will be me!
The Eternity Devil!
The floor's tilting!
Give me Denji's heart!
Somebody, anybody, kill Denji!
Please make him dead!
We're running out of time!
Let's just feed him to the devil!
I'm using the sword.
You okay with that, Himeno?
Himeno?!
Whoa, lady! What the hell?!
We can probably get out of here \Nif he uses that sword,
but the pact is one that takes a lot \Nof years off Aki's life in exchange.
He's got too much to live for.
I'm sorry, Denji.
Damn it!
Hey, get off!
Let me go!
Die!
He might be a piece of shit that\N deserves being stabbed a time or two...
But he wants the Gun Devil dead.
And I... can't kill it by myself.
To do that, I need Devil Hunters \Nwith the guts to fight it.
The more, the better...
Even if it costs some of my own life...
I'm not letting Denji die.
Power! You're the Blood Fiend, right?
Can you keep him from bleeding out?
I only have total control over my own blood.
The blood of others is a challenge.
But I suppose I'd need a new\N cook if topknot died.
Given that, I have little choice.
What do we do?
What do we do?!
Aki... Aki! Aki, what do we do?!
I-It's not my fault!
You! This is because of you!
If you just let it eat you, \Nthis would all be over!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Guess it's snack time, then.
Oh, thank goodness.
I'm not gonna go down smooth, though.
So if I manage to kill this fucking devil...
I still expect to get that kiss!
Have you any plan to win?
It's gonna hurt real bad, \Nbut I'll get my chainsaws out.
Ch-Chainsaws?
I dunno what this devil's deal is, \Nbut it's scared of my chainsaws.
That's why it didn't try to kill me, \Nand wanted you guys to do it instead.
And I remember it was crying \Nabout pain when it got attacked...
So I figure, if I tear it up until \Nit can't take the pain no more,
it'll wanna kill itself!
A very devilish idea indeed.
I can't believe you did that for me.
Nobody asked you. Asshole.
I'm through with owing \Nanybody anything, got it?
So once you're out of here, we're even!
I can't believe you did that for me.
Nobody asked you. Asshole.
I'm through with owing \Nanybody anything, got it?
So once you're out of here, we're even!
It's over...
I knew you were alive, Chainsaw!
Yeow!
All better!
This is pointless, Chainsaw!
The pain!
It hurts!
You won't find my heart in here!
You can't kill me!
A devil?!
This bodes ill.
Denji's losing blood ceaselessly.
When he's lost too much, \Nhis chainsaws will retract.
You are so much weaker now.
How far you have fallen, Chainsaw?!
My chainsaws are in?
Need more blood!
You've failed!
Die!
Chainsaw!
This blood might seriously taste like shit...
But watching you shriek in pain...
Makes it sweet like strawberry jam!
The hunters that devils fear...
are the ones with a couple of screws loose.
Sahara had his head on straight...
So he died.
Same goes for Kinouchi, \Nand Subaru, and Sasaki. All sane.
They were reasonable enough \Nto fear attacks from a devil,
and that fear made the devils stronger.
You been working with Aki for a while now.\N What do you think about him?
Is his head on straight?
I wouldn't say that about anyone \Nwho's trying to kill the Gun Devil.
Didn't you join Public Safety because\N you were after the Gun Devil, too?
You got any screws loose?
No, sir.
Exactly.
Most hunters, including you, \Nare out to put the Gun Devil down.
They're earnest. Honest. Straightforward.
And that means the devils know \Nexactly how to fuck with them.
But there's no telling what \Na crazy person's thinking.
And even devils are afraid \Nof what they don't understand.
You're drinking too much again, master.
See, that's being sensible again.
Can't be unhinged without \Nloosening the screws a bit every day.
And if you're still visiting your \Npartners' graves every month,
then yours are still pretty tight.
I'm heading home.
Aki's still a punk, so make \Nsure to work him over.
I'll take it one step at a time.
Not good enough.
The kid's serious about \Ncollecting the meat chunks, right?
He's gonna actually find \Nthe Gun Devil if he does.
No...
No, no, no, no, no, no—
No.
Aki, you wanna join \Nthe private sector with me?
I received a pretty generous offer!
Instead of chasing the Gun,
we could go out for lunch, \Nsee a movie on the way home,
and really enjoy ourselves.
If you wanna go out \Nfor drinks, I'll join you.
But I have no intention \Nof ever going private.
And I'll take your almond tofu.
Then hand me a cigarette in exchange.
If Aki fights the Gun Devil, he's gonna die.
Not because we're too weak,
or because it's the kind of devil that \Ncan kill hundreds of people in seconds.
It's because Aki's cool, \Nand serious, and kind...
and normal, like most people.
But...
Take that!
Ow, ow!
It...
It's over.
But him?
Eureka, dude.
I cut you up, and you bleed.
I drink that blood and heal!
I'm a fucking perpetual motion machine!
That Nobel Prize is mine!
I've never seen anyone crazier than him,
so maybe he can kill the Gun Devil!
Pain...
Ow, ow...
It hurts...
You still alive, Aki?
How long...
How long has it been?
About three days since \Nyou got stabbed, I think?
Meowy...
Let's all go out for drinks.
Since it's over... I'm gonna sleep a bit.
It's over?
This is my weakness...
It's my heart.
Please kill me.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
It hurts...
What, already?!
I was still having fun! \NIt was like being in a pool!
AUTOMATED
We're out.
Got a piece of the Gun Devil's flesh,\N the sky is clear...
And I'm feeling good, \Nlike I just took a huge shit.
It's like I'm floating...
Whoa there.
He's out...
Makes sense, considering he was fighting \Nthe devil the whole time without sleeping.
We'll get Aki and Denji to a hospital.
You two head back \Nto the office and check in.
A welcoming party?
Yep.
Since the full Division 4 \Nis finally assembled,
we ought to get to know each other better,
and deal with some of our outstanding issues.
What issues?
Well, the thing is, Kobeni and Arai \Nare talking about quitting Public Safety.
Not only are they afraid of the devils,
they feel pretty guilty \Nabout trying to kill Denji, too.
You tried to kill him, too.
I know, right?!
Kids these days! They're so sensitive.
Would it kill them to be a little bolder?
Over drinks, they'll be able to \Napologize to Denji easily,
and we'll be able to \Nconvince them to not quit.
You're just in this for drinks.
It wasn't much, but I found \Na chunk of its flesh.
If we're doing this, \Nit needs to be this week.
Why's that?
If we're having a drinking party, \NI want to invite Ms. Makima.
She's going on a business trip \Nto Kyoto next week.
With so many devils targeting Denji, \Nshe's looking into getting reinforcements.
So the party needs to be this week.
Be honest with me.
What do you think Denji is?
That devil seemed to know about him,
and I've never seen anything \Nlike what he turned into.
But the biggest mystery is how much \NMs. Makima seems to be interested in him.
She used to travel all the time, \Nbut she's stuck to Tokyo lately,
and that's probably because of Denji.
Does she know his secret?
Wanna get her hammered and ask about it?
Cheers!
Man, all this stuff smells awesome!
This is enough food for a lifetime!
That's the stuff!
Oh, here we go.
This is nuts!
Here's your plate.
Where do I even start? \NIt all smells great.
This is good. It's been six months \Nsince I last had anything to drink.
I only drink a bit at home, too.
Away with you!
The sashimi shall all be mine!
What even is this? Looks tasty!
Sorry... I got a little lost.
Kobe, Kobe! Right over here!
Ms. Makima says she'll be late.
Three parfaits.
And then...
Three shiratama dumpling trays.
I've never had anything this good before.
You send most of your pay home, right?
Be sure to eat your fill.
Hands off, you scoundrel!
The fried chicken is all mine!
You didn't bring your Fiend, Fushi?
They're a little too scary \Nfor a place like this.
I envy how reasonable yours is, Hayakawa.
Hey!
You're young, so order \Nwhatever you want! And eat up!
Damn it! I can't read most of these kanji...
m 225 15 l 225 48 422 48 422 15
So... about that kiss...
I'm too bashful to do it right now.
Let me drink a bit more first.
I'll make it a juicy one, too.
So will you forgive us \Nfor trying to kill you?
Dude, all is forgiven! Super forgiven!
This is a welcoming party for the rookies, \Nso stand up and introduce yourselves!
Your name, age, and the devil \Nyou're contracted with!
Don't reveal your devil contract in public.
You shouldn't share that \Nwith anyone you don't trust.
Man, you never loosen up, do you?
Aw, it's fine! It's probably fine.
I wanna know hobbies, too.
They tell you a lot about a person.
I'm Denji. I'm 16, if I remember right.
My hobbies are eating and sleeping!
Yikes, that is young.
You didn't drink, did you?!
Just tea.
I'm Hirokazu Arai! I'm 22 years old!
I've got a contract with the Fox Devil!
My hobby is writing haiku!
That's the same devil as Hayakaptain.
The Fox Devil is friendly toward humans.
So many hunters make contracts\N with the Fox Devil.
But only hotties get to call \Non the Fox Devil's head!
As devils go, the Fox is down bad.
I'm Kobeni Higashiyama.
I'm 20...
I've got a devil contract... \Nbut it's a secret.
My hobby is eating tasty things.
Isn't her outfit cute?
Yeah.
It's a hand-me-down from my sister.
Kobeni has eight sisters. Isn't that crazy?
Hey, where's your rookie, Fushi?
I'm sad to report that they \Nwere killed yesterday.
Rest in peace!
They will be... mist... pissed... missed?
Already wasted, huh?
Do people really die that often?
Public Safety handles the devils \Ntoo tough for the private sector.
Yeah, we're always dropping like flies.
No one who joined up at the \Nsame time as me is still alive.
Denji's not gonna die, \Ncuz he wants a smooch!
Himeno gets really friendly \Nwhen she's drunk.
I'm pretty sure she's kissed everyone here,\N apart from the rookies.
There's no escaping her.
That's a guaranteed kiss!
Today's the day... of my first kiss.
What kiss?
Ms. Makima!
Excuse me, I'd like a draft beer.
Have a seat, Ms. Makima.
I've never seen her in person before.
So, are you kissing someone, Denji?
No, ma'am!
Aw, are we not gonna kiss, Denji?!
We are!
Excuse me. Another beer.
So, what's this about kisses?
I don't want Ms. Makima \Nto see me kiss Himeno.
No smoochies?
But I want a kiss with tongue \Njust as bad!
I've gotta try and change the subject!
Ms. Makima! Y'know, I got one \Nof them Gun Devil thingies!
Yes, I heard. That's very impressive, Denji.
We've never seen devils appearing with \NGun Devil flesh this frequently before.
Given how the most recent one \Nwas targeting Denji,
something must be going on.
Do you know what Denji's deal is, ma'am?
Relinquish that!
That, too, is mine!
I'll tell you if you can outdrink me.
Two more beers, please.
I want in on that! Make it three!
Horse sashimi! Fried chicken! \NAnd more horse sashimi!
Fried chicken!
That's mine, too.
Another beer, if you would.
You're pretty impressive, Power.
There aren't a lot of Fiends \Nwho can control their urge to kill.
A feat of my advanced IQ!
Is IQ part of it? How high is yours, then?
Um... 100?
Is that high?
I think my score was around 100, too.
Then it was 120.
If I remember right, Fushi's is high.
Specifically, 134.
Wow, must be proud enough\Nto actually remember it.
If I recall, mine was 500?
Perhaps 1000?
Oh my.
She's watching!
Ms. Makima's watching.
But what is this?
The kiss is afoot!
Is that a tongue I feel?
Feels good... soft! Really soft!
What the hell?! It's her tongue...
But it's melting in my mouth?!
That's... not... a tongue!
It's puke!
Well, that's traumatic.
Uh-oh...
Excuse me, can we get \Nsomething to wipe this up?
Oh, this isn't good! Not good at all!
Denji will swallow anything \Nremotely nutritious!
Pochita!
I found something edible!
Check it out, Pochita!
Those rats are chowing on some drunk's puke!
Eating puke! What a joke!
What kinda mammals are they?!
Unbelievable... Himeno has \Nabsolutely no restraint.
My method for throwing up \Nworks pretty well, right?
I used to look after my mom when \Nshe came home drunk from work.
Not that it makes me as good \Na Devil Hunter as you.
I'm pretty jealous.
Jealous?!
Dude... My first kiss tasted like barf!
And you're jealous?!
I'll see Hayakawa and his household home.
You wanna drop by somewhere else?
I drank a lot...
Ms. Makima paid the tab tonight, \Neveryone, so show your gratitude.
Nothing tastes better than \Ndrinks someone else paid for.
Yep.
Huh? Where's Denji?
I saw Himeno pick him up \Nand walk off somewhere.
It's dark... So dark...
Where the hell am I?
Water... Water... Water...
Come to think of it, the puke \Ngirl gave me a barf kiss.
Damn it! Water, water...
Huh... It's Den-Den-Denji?
What are you doing in my place?
Did I bring you here?
Huh?
I'm so dizzy... What the hell?
Y'know, I noticed you're \Nhead over heels for Makima.
My head's spinning...
You could do better than \Nthat bitch, seriously.
You and Aki, fawning all over her! Ugh...
Seriously!
Moo-ve on!
Wanna do it?
m 199 189 l 326 189 326 231 199 231
This is good. \NIt's been too long.
I don't drink\Nmuch at home, too.
Kobe, Kobe!\NRight over here!
m 353 144 l 430 144 430 155 353 155
m 385 191 l 385 221 480 221 480 191
m 199 189 l 326 189 326 231 199 231
Be kept\NBe killed