If you want to save this cat, \Nthen bring me a human.
One life is worth as little as any other.
And this is only a cat.
So why do I run? \NWhy do I search for a human?
Is it to save Meowy?
Such a foolish reason.
I love blood.
The taste, the smell, \Nthe sense of mortality...
And then... there is something \NI only recently realized:
The blood is warm...
And feels pleasant.
Why did you save me?
I attempted to kill you.
Such a foolish reason.
Forgive my deceit.
Since Meowy is safe...
You may fondle my chest.
Hell yeah!
Holy shit! Ow!
That hurts!
Can you move?
Not even a finger.
Take Meowy and flee, please.
Damn it, not enough chainsaw...
I must be low on blood.
And after I finally found him...
It's you, right? The one who killed Batty.
He was my man, y'know?!
Oh... but you're actually \Npretty cute yourself.
You're my type, so I'll let you go!
What about them?
They die.
Then you can die, too.
He can fight so fiercely...
To merely fondle a chest?
Is this a joke?
How'd a little pupper \Nlike you kill my Batty?
Y'know, he and I shared a dream: \Nkilling and eating all of humanity.
A pipe dream, but a noble one, \Nand a romantic one.
And now this little \Nyipping dog has ruined it.
You're cute enough that I regret it...
But you still need to die.
I'm not dying before I cop a feel.
That is ridiculous!
To think he was killed by someone \Nwith such a trashy dream.
Alas, poor Batty...
Such a foolish reason.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
Everybody wants to trash-talk my plans...
It's revenge this,
protect my family that,
and save a cat, too!
Blah, blah, blah!
I guess your fancy dreams \Nmake you guys hot shit, huh?!
How about we have us a dream battle, then?! \NHow about that?!
If I murderize you,
that means your dream's \Nweaker than fondling a tit!
Even your howls are cute!
But y'know what they say about \Nlittle dogs barking! Yap, yap, yap!
Okay! I'll gobble you up, then!
Go ahead...
If you can beat me in the dream battle!
Demoniacal...
Time to eat...
Kon.
Huh... Huh?
Looks like she's the Leech Devil. \NMay I swallow?
Do it.
The Leech Devil's extermination is confirmed.
I want the rookies handling search \Nand rescue, plus assisting with the evac.
Yes, sir!
Himeno, you've got seniority, \Nso keep watch for more devils.
On it.
Dream battle... Gonna... My dream battle...
You and the Blood Fiend \Nneed to be debriefed.
And Meowy?
Have the cat sent to a veterinarian \Nfor a thorough checkup.
I found your arm.
A blood infusion was all \Nit needed to reattach.
You really are like a devil.
You seemed pretty friendly \Nwith that devil back there.
I saw.
You really don't know a thing, huh?
Devil Hunters form contracts with \Ndevils in order to fight against them.
I've got a contract with the Fox Devil.
In exchange for power, \NI offer up a bit of my body as food.
It was some skin this time.
Sounds painful.
Devils yearn for the deaths of humans.
The same goes for Fiends.
Power seems cool, though.
The surveillance cameras caught \Nyou two headed to your patrol area.
Paused
And the house that we believe \Nwas housing the Bat Devil
contained a lot of your spilt blood.
The Blood Fiend tried to kill you, didn't she?
I don't know why, but you're trying \Nto protect a devil. Again.
I dunno... is that how it happened?
My daughter would like \Nto meet the chainsaw guy.
Thank you.
The devil threatened to eat \Nme back at the office,
but now that I think about it, he was \Nwearing a Public Safety uniform.
I'd like to thank him.
"Don't give a shit about \Nsaving some dude," he says!
And then the devil throws \Nmy car with me in it!
It was a devil with a chainsaw \Ncoming out of its head...
If I dig deeper into this, \Nand report it to the higher-ups,
it'd mean the Blood Fiend gets disposed of\N along with you, since you covered for her.
But there were no fatalities.
So, if you're willing to accept one condition, \NI'll let what happened slide.
You need to do what I tell you to.
You're a dumbass and a brat \Nwith no clue about right and wrong.
I've been doing this longer, so I'm pretty\N sure I have some grasp of social ethics.
All you need to do to protect \Nthis lifestyle is listen to me.
How about it? If you follow, \NI want an answer.
Sure. I'll keep it in mind.
You can relax.
I might not be after some \Nbig-deal goal like you guys,
and I might dream small.
But I'm as serious about this as you are.
You can count on me.
Try and learn some manners in the meantime.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
You see? Am I not innocent?
Now, would you kindly take these off?
Is this a good idea?
When this cutie-Fiend kills somebody,
it's gonna be your responsibility, \Nfor letting her live.
We're Devil Hunters.
Whether they're devils or Fiends,
if they're handy, \Nwe should put them to work.
But they're still the enemy. \NWe're just making use of them.
We're not making friends.
Come in.
Excuse me.
And he claims they "were outside \Nthe patrol zone before they knew it,"
and that they discovered a house that\N"looked like it had a super-nasty devil in it,"
which is where they encountered \Nthe Bat Devil.
Denji used his chainsaws to\N exterminate the Bat Devil,
and then came under attack \Nby the Leech Devil...
Which Division 4 exterminated.
There were no traces of Gun flesh \Nin either the Bat or Leech Devil's heads.
That concludes my report.
Well done.
But Denji and Power managed to get awfully \Nfar without anyone noticing, didn't they?
I'd chalk that up to them \Nbeing unbelievably stupid.
Leaving the approved area \Nis against regulations.
Considering there were no fatalities,
and that we were able to get rid of \Ntwo devils, I think it's worth overlooking.
Understood.
If you'll excuse me, ma'am.
You seem a little more \Nflexible now, Hayakawa.
Is that Denji's influence, I wonder?
I doubt it.
I haven't changed at all.
How's he up so early?
What's for lunch?
Curry.
Sweet!
The hell's this? A devil?
What a pitiful home this is!
I'd like you to put Power up \Nin one of your rooms, Hayakawa.
I think you'll make a good leash \Nfor the two of them.
Stop right there, Meowy!
It seems you've got quite a feast!
Damn it, who said you could come in?!
'Tis mine now!
Gimme my super toast back!
Oh... okay.
It'd be a little odd to have her \Nstaying at the office indefinitely.
Okay.
You don't need to worry. \NPower said she would behave.
It'll be fine.
Vegetables are revolting!
Away!
Carrot!
Don't fling your vegetables!
Damn it...
Show some respect to the farmers \Nwho grew the veggies, devil!
The toilet?
I prefer to only occasionally \Nflush my feces.
Flush it!
It stinks.
I prefer to only occasionally bathe.
Get in there!
You reek!
You two are absurd.
How delicate these humans be.
Aren't they, Meowy?
Can't believe she just shows up \Nand starts raising hell.
Do devils not flush the toilet?
Didn't eat her veggies either.
You there...
Hey, Shit Devil! Your turds are stuck \Nto the damn toilet and won't come off!
We had a deal, did we not?
You may fondle my chest.
So, fondle!
Come now, what's the matter? \NAren't you pleased?
Commence your fondling.
I have stipulations, however.
You have earned three squeezes of my breast.
Three?
One for your rescue of Meowy.
A second for slaying the Bat Devil.
And a third for protecting me from topknot!
I had no intention of actually letting you,
but your efforts have earned \Nyou these three squeezes.
Squeeze them gratefully.
She's an angel!
BLAAAARGH!
Lalalalah
Denji,\NHear\NMe\NOut
It feels so good!
What the...?
Breast pads.
A wondrous invention that \Nmakes your bosom look bigger.
Now! Two squeezes remain.
And now! The final fondling!
There, done! All done!
What did you think? Was it not fantastic?
How lucky for you, to grasp \Nsuch splendorous things!
And now we are even!
With Meowy saved, I have no real reason \Nto hunt devils any longer,
There's lots of stuff I could say, but... Huh?
yet there's no escaping Makima!
So I will aid you all with your duty!
I'm sure the pleasure is all yours!
Meowy! Off to bed we go!
That's it?
This is good!
Seconds would be splendid!
I'll eat yours, if you won't have it!
You little...!
Where shall we slaughter devils today?
Hey.
Hey!
Chop!
This is the form apology \Nfor the damage to the buildings.
This is for verifying \Nthe disposal of the devils' bodies.
Then there's this, from the Ministry of Land, \NInfrastructure, Transport and Tourism.
You'll need to stamp it, here and here.
I hate making you do all this paperwork.
It's almost like killing \Nthe Bat Devil was a bad thing.
Is something bothering you, Denji?
Y'know, I...
There's something I was chasing after, \Nand I finally managed to get it.
But once I did, it wasn't...
as big of a deal as I thought.
Now I'm wondering, if I go after \Nsomething else, and get my hands on it,
am I just gonna think \NI was happier during the chase?
That's, like... total bullshit, isn't it?
What exactly are you talking about, Denji?
I touched boobs for the first time,\N but it wasn't that great.
Denji...
I believe that, when it comes to sex,
the better you understand \Nthe other person, the better it feels.
But it's hard to understand \Nhow someone else feels.
So, start with observing \Nthe hand, carefully.
How long are their fingers?
Are their palms cold?
Are they warm?
What's the shape of their ears?
Ever had your finger bitten?
B-Bit...?
Remember this.
So that even if you can't see,
you'll be able to tell it's me, \Nfrom how hard I'm biting.
Memorize it.
I... got it.
Denji...
I'd like to ask you to do something for me.
Can I?
Yeah.
I want you to beat the Gun Devil.
Gun Devil?
It appeared in America 13 years ago, \Nbut nobody knows where it is now.
It's a very strong devil \Nthat all hunters want to kill.
But I happen to think that you can kill it.
Because you're not like any \Nof the other Devil Hunters.
And if you're able to kill the Gun Devil,
I'll make any wish of yours come true.
You're saying if your Denji\N kills the Gun Devil,
Miss Makima's gonna make \Nany wish of his come true?
So... like, I mean...
You're saying if your Denji\N kills the Gun Devil,
Miss Makima's gonna make \Nany wish of his come true?
Anything, like... even se—
I said anything, Denji.
Holy shit! Is that even allowed?!
It's only allowed because this devil \Nis so strong and bad, mind you.
People were trying to profit off of guns
as a counter-measure against \Ndevils across the world,
which resulted in an increase \Nin crime and conflict.
The news focused on it \Nnon-stop for a while,
with people more afraid \Nof gun violence than ever.
Then a major armed terrorist \Nattack happened in America.
That was the day the Gun Devil appeared.
"This is where I live," said the city mouse.
The Country Mouse and the City Mouse
And, oh what a big house it was!
The city mouse's family—
Dad!
Let's play catch outside.
Taiyo doesn't feel well. \NFind something you can play by yourself.
He never does.
I don't remember him feeling good.
You're the older brother. \NBe good and play by yourself.
I...
I wanna play with him.
Quit following me.
You're so annoying... I said cut it out!
I'm gonna play by myself.
Gotcha!
Stupid! I said cut it out!
It's cold...
If you catch a cold, \NI'm gonna get in trouble.
Your hands won't get cold \Nif we play catch, right?
Go grab a glove from the house.
Yes!
In a little under five minutes, \N1.2 million people were killed.
The Gun Devil hasn't been seen since.
Fear of devils across the board \Nincreased as a result,
making them all stronger than ever before.
Gun control got a lot more severe \Nin an attempt to weaken the Gun Devil...
Along with increased censorship of the news.
I'm not sure I understand, but...
Let's say this thing's so strong, \Nit's hard to understand.
Do you think you can beat it, Denji?
Well... I'd say...
If I bust out all the stops,
it'll be a peace of cake.
In that case...
First, we'll need to actually \Nfind the Gun Devil.
How exactly are we gonna do that, anyway?
These are pieces of the Gun Devil \Nthat we've collected.
It's so fast, pieces of it \Nare torn off just from moving.
If a devil eats some of this,
no matter what their nature, \Nthey become more powerful.
See how they stick together?
Because of how powerful the Gun Devil is,
once the chunks of flesh \Nreach a certain size,
they start to be attracted \Nto the original body.
So if we can make this piece bigger,
it'll lead us to the Gun Devil.
Got one.
So it really was snacking \Non a piece of the Gun.
Explains how such \Na wimpy devil got so strong.
But did it find that piece, \Nor did someone serve it up?
Doesn't change what our job is.
We keep killing devils,
and eventually, we'll find him.
Public Safety's received a request \Nfor devil extermination.
A devil has been spotted inside of a hotel.
No confirmation on the status \Nof the hotel's guests.
Several of the civilian devil hunters \Nwho initially went in have been found dead.
It's believed the target has \Nconsumed a piece of the Gun Devil.
We're sending six agents from Public Safety \NDevil Extermination Special Division 4.
It's hiding somewhere in this hotel.
And this is no ordinary devil.
It's eaten a piece of the Gun Devil's flesh.
Maybe it's the Gun Devil for real?
The more flesh, the stronger the attraction. \NThe reaction's not big enough.
Huh, guess not.
How amusing... Give that thing to me!
I thought I told you two \Nto work on your manners.
Who the hell's gonna suck up \Nto you for no reason?
How foolish and conceited these humans be!
Mr. Hayakawa.
Sir.
Good.
Sweet!
Dude, he's so easy.
Hayakawa!
Considering we're about \Nto fight some devils...
Can we really trust these two \Nto watch our backs?
One's a Fiend, and the other is some punk...
I'm not sure about this.
We can't let them watch our backs.
On extermination missions, \Nthey'll be taking point.
If they try to run \Nor switch sides, we kill them.
You're treating us like livestock!
You two don't get rights.
He's super pissed.
Must be from this morning.
Perhaps our prank went too far?
You call that a prank?! I could kill you!
Yikes! What happened?
Aki, you can't just be harsh \Nall the time, y'know?
She's right! The bat almost killed me, \Nand now there's more work?!
I want a reward!
Got it! I'll take one for the team.
Whoever kills this devil will win...
a kiss on the cheek from yours truly!
That's... You shouldn't do that!
A young woman who's not married \Nshouldn't be so... indecent!
But doesn't a reward help with motivation?
Right?
I'm not gonna sweat the kisses.
Don't worry about it. I'm plenty motivated.
Oh?
I got my sights set on someone \Nfor a first kiss already.
I'm gonna find all these meat chunks \Nor whatever for her.
So, until the Gun Devil's dead, \Nno smooching for me.
That's a hell of a thing \Nto say in front of Aki!
Besides, I learned something real important.
Sex stuff feels better when it's \Ntwo people who get each other.
I don't even know your name, \Nso I ain't after your lips!
Then, if you kill the devil, Denji...
I'll give you a kiss... with tongue.
Hey, hold it!
It's dangerous to run off solo! Stop!
th Floor
Damn, I love teasing boys!
Oh man, what are we gonna do?
I yearn for blood.
It's dangerous! You need to stop!
Himeno's been nice enough to train me \Nfor the last six months!
If the alternative is letting \Nsome thug like you kiss her...
Then I'll take that kiss on the cheek!
Move!
I don't want some dude \Nall over me! It's nasty!
Say what?!
Die! I'm after a way \Nbigger goal than you, dude!
I wish to join you!
Shut up! I don't wanna hear that \Nfrom someone newer than me!
What's your take on the rookies, Himeno?
Man, shut up!
More of this! Yes!
I'd say Arai's not super competent, \Nbut makes up for it in motivation.
Get him, get him!
Meanwhile, Kobeni's got the moves, \Nbut she's really timid.
You think any of the four rookies \Nhave a shot of surviving, Aki?
It's a duel to the death!
You get the picture, now?
regardless of how strong \NI thought they were.
You are not kissing Himeno!
Asshole... I'm gonna kill you!
That's not really an answer.
Power... you're dead, too!
You too, shorty.
But why?!
Himeno...
This is your new partner.
He's rude, but I trained him \Nto be of some use.
Try and get along.
I'm Aki.
Nice to meet you.
Are you gonna be any help?
Well... I think so.
You're gonna be my sixth partner.
The others all died.
They all died because they were useless.
Don't die on me, Aki.
Gotta say, I'm not seeing \Nany devils around here.
Does that meat chunk of yours even work?
So tired...
Aki...
Incoming.
Got it.
It floats?!
The battle is joined!
Damnable devil! Did you see \Nhow it floated in fear of me?!
No, no, that's my power.
Say what?
I've got a contract with the Ghost Devil.
I served up my right eye in exchange \Nfor being able to use a ghost's right hand.
My ghost hand's invisible \Nand strong. Pretty slick, right?
How about it, Aki? \NHas he got any of the Gun's flesh?
No strong reaction. This isn't the one.
I see... guess we better keep heading up.
Is it wise to blather on about \Nyour powers in my presence?
Are you people not meant to hold my reins?
Knowing about our powers makes \Nfor better teamwork, right?
Besides, I've got a few tricks \Nup my sleeve, so I'm not worried.
Truly?
So what would you do if I said \NI was going to kill this one?
Put the weapon away.
If you misbehave, \NI can always choke you to death.
Can't... touch it...
I'd prefer if we got along. It's easier!
I will devour you in time!
You better not. I'm trying to get a kiss.
Do you guys not get that the devil \Nis still around? Can't you pipe...
Huh?
She does look like \Nshe'd be unpleasant raw.
What is it?
That sounds pervy, dude.
We were... on our way to \Nthe 9th floor from the 8th, right?
Perhaps boiling or frying...
Cook your own ass, stupid.
th Floor
But this is the 8th floor.
You probably read it wrong.
It's not that! Something's going on here!
I'm gonna double check.
I know! Grilled like a steak!
Steak?!
I wanna try steak!
Huh?
Arai... just now... you were \Ngoing downstairs, right?